Yeah, I see you upset
You living a lie at work,
you’re dreamers at best
I made this for you, I
figured you needed a vest
I'll come out with a mask
next when I aim for your head
I'm speaking direct
Hit the bullseye with my eyes closed
Third eye looking through a rifle
They could never get me for my soul
I can smell the bull with my wide nose
You guys all over the place
I got the scope of the place
and the codes to your safe
You dug the hole to your grave
This is just business so
put your emotions away
Oh, I see you upset
Cold heart, got the burner
Try me, put the heat to your chest
Get involved, make a call
Couple shots to your dog, I'm a vet
It's bigger than me, it's my team
We gon' need some respect
Plus I need me a check
Pulled up to your plug
Never paid a nigga, I take interest
Only flexing when it come to fitness
Get your hood lit up like it's Christmas
Way too many shots, got it lit quick
Catch a case, it get dismissed
That was old news, shot the witness
Got your lady next on my hit list
To these virgin eyes, I'm a beast
Off the leash, need a vet
I guess they see I'm a threat, y'all pussy
I got hitters on call,
that'll really get you wet
I'ma need some respect, don't
come through here dripping
Cause this heat make you sweat
Better keep you a vest,
I'ma keep you in check
I see how you living, we different
You got me started ignition,
like this my tradition
I pull up and hit with precision
I do not need no permission,
I feel like a hitman
For hitman I’ll murder ya mistress
Leave without leaving a
witness, I'm feeling ambitious
I kill anybody that listen, it
really just come down to business
I know why they upset
They just mad that we next
All this ice around my neck
Benji here chasing a check
Sick of Dulce pass me the Henny
They can go around, know we got plenty
Hit it lit quick, made a quick flip
Not knowing that the devil was in me
Cause I got free smoke for the freeloaders
Weed gassing up their ego
Till I roll up on them like a steamroller
Shoot them down then I reload it
I know why they upset
They just mad that we next
All this ice around my neck
Benji head chasing a check
Oh they upset
They upset
They probably mad
They got finessed
I'm not impressed
They not a threat
I know why they upset
They mad they mad
Probably hating cause we next
Haters hate to see success